I said I want to dream of sushi,
but with what you did,
it's like I'll have a nightmare.
What's that?
Paella negra.
Even a stray dog who hasn't eaten for months
won't eat that.
So you made a mango pie
where mangoes were harvested
from just anywhere?
That is not okay.
I guess you're aware
that they are just playing with you.
I can feel that they're challenging me.
But don't worry,
tomorrow, I'll be okay again.
I won't give up.
Remember, you made a promise to me
that the moment you get tired there,
you'll come home here as soon as possible.
Can you still cook
for the naughty grandsons of Grandpa Garp?
Or will you follow
what you promised to Mother and Father?
Never ever give up, you can do it.
Why are the Ferells like that
when it comes to food?
The late wife of Don Ferell, Dona Amanda,
is a very good cook.
When Dona Amanda died,
it was like they don't care about each other.
Do you know the saying,
"the way to a man's heart
is through his stomach"?
Your mother and I won't be a couple
if not for this recipe.
Father, what are you cooking?
This is what you call, "a heart that loves".
So, who is my secret admirer?
In fairness, he's very sweet.
He sent messages using a dove.
Whoever said that romance is dead?
Your hair is long...
Effort.
He could give... chocolates or flowers,
but messages using a dove.
I even beat Harry Potter.
It's like I'm studying at Hogwart's
School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.
I'm also happy I'll always taste
your loving heart.
Is it Owen?
Well...
It seems you're in deep thought.
You startled me.
Do you know what's more startling?
What, did you convince Don Ferell
to make his grandsons eat your food?
Yes, Mr. Dencio.
I told you.
You can work as a cook here in the mansion.
I wouldn't have thought about it
if not for you.
You have a lot of insights about the Ferells,
that's why, thank you.
What's with you? No problem.
I'm already happy that I'm able to help you.
Mr. Dencio, I have a question.
Is there someone in the mansion
who's taking care of the doves?
A dove?
There's no one that I know
here in the mansion.
Is there someone taking care
of the doves here?
None.
Do you have a pet dove?
None, but I have a lizard.
Do you want a lizard?
No, I don't want.
How about our neighbors,
do they have pet doves?
Neighbors?
With how vast the property of Don Ferell is,
I don't think we have neighbors here.
Wait, why are you interested in doves?
Not really.
How about the Ferells?
Do you know who among them is fond of doves?
With doves, none.
It seems it's Owen who likes animals.
Really?
Yes, I remember.
Owen wanted to get a puppy,
but it didn't push through,
because Serafica is allergic.
Yes, that's right.
It's Owen who is the animal lover here.
Hey, why are you smiling that way?
It looks like you won the lottery.
No, Mr. Dencio I'm just happy
when I meet someone
who happens to be an animal lover like me.
- Oh, is that so?
- Yes.
You know, I'm an animal lover too.
- I am fond of fish.
- Fish?
Yes, fish.
Then why are you eating fish?
That's right.
I'm a "fishtetarian".
Go ahead and eat.
Come on, Florence.
Here, eat.
It's delicious, right?
- Fish be with you.
- Fish be with you?
I guess my hunch is right.
No matter how proud and naughty
these guys are,
they're all close to their grandfather.
They just need a little push.
Success!
Are you just a dream, or will it come true?
He's cute, and of all the Ferells,
he's the only one I haven't heard talking.
Why?
Is he a weirdo?
Or he sounds like a frog?
Kokak, kokak, kokak.
It's so delicious.
Did he see me looking at him?
Just kidding!
There.
My goodness...
Did he catch me looking at him?
I hope not.
He might think that I have a desire for him.
Hello, I don't have a desire for him.
Nothing, nothing, nothing!
Stop it, Florencia.
You're thinking a lot of nonsense, you witch.
Well, you don't have a desire for Nero.
Nothing, nothing, nothing!
Is there really nothing?
Grandpa asked me to come here.
He wants to talk to you.
So, this is the tone of his voice.
He doesn't sound like a frog.
Did you hear what I said?
Yes, frog.
Yes, Grandpa Garp is asking for me.
I'll go to him right away.
I want to thank you, Florence.
Your idea that we eat together
with my grandsons
is making this old man happy these days.
Initially, I admit that I want to pinch
my grandsons' mouths
because they were all frowning
when I said we will eat together.
Good thing, these days,
they're starting to be comfortable
eating together during meal time.
That's what my mother taught me.
Food doesn't become delicious
because of its delicious ingredients.
It becomes more delicious
when you're eating it with your loved ones.
Your parents are good people, Florence.
They should be proud of you
because it looks like
they've raised you well.
Oh, don't give too much credit
to Mother and Father.
I was born so beautiful and kind, perfect!
See, Grandpa Garp, I'm a very ideal daughter.
That's just a joke.
And it's true that
Mother and Father are so kind,
that's why, I owe it to them
whoever I am right now.
So, I'll do everything for them
and I won't replace them with anyone else.
We are lucky that you became
a part of our family, Florence.
Where are we going?
I need to drop by GU
to talk to the Academic Dean
to know the academic status of my grandsons.
School is about to start.
This is Gyronella University.
The best university in the country.
- Hi, Dean.
- Welcome, Don Ferell.
Welcome.
Florence?
Florence, Don Ferell is calling you.
I'm sorry.
I got distracted.
GU is really beautiful.
Do you need anything?
No, I just wanted to tell you
that you can stay in the car with Dencio.
Okay. No problem.
We'll wait for you here.
- Okay.
- Shall we?
Shall we?
Beautiful...
It looks like a mall.
Mr. Dencio, can I call my Mother and Father?
- Okay, go ahead.
- I'll just stroll around.
- Go ahead.
- I will be quick.
Mother, Father?
- Don't go too far.
- I'll be quick.
Someone is calling.
Hey, Florence.
Why are you calling?
- Is that Florence?
- Yes.
My child!
Is there a problem?
Father, there's no problem,
but guess where I am right now?
I hope you're still on earth, my child.
Yes, I'll get mad if you went ahead of me.
What's with you?
I'm still here on earth,
but I'm in the coolest place.
You're in the Gyronella University, Florence?
Yes, Mother. Yes, Father!
Welcome to Gyronella University.
Welcome to GU.
Let's stroll around. Let's go!
Go ahead, my child.
Let's start here...
Mother, Father,
I think this is their soccer field.
Look, it's so big.
Let's try it, Mother.
Excuse me, can I try?
There you go, Mother...
Here, Mother. One, two, three...
Yes! Yes! Goal!
Thank you!
Someone is trying out
for the volleyball team here.
Let me... Let me!
Alyssa Valdez.
Thank you. Bye!
Let's go here.
Mother, Father,
this is their basketball court.
Someone is playing.
There...
There!
I can do that better.
Let me try, Mister...
Can you hold this, please? Here it is...
Dwight Ramos in three, two, one!
MVP, Mother!
Thanks! Bye!
Let's go here, Mother!
Father, they also have
something different here.
They have a great wall of climbing.
Mother, I'll try it out.
Just stay there and watch.
Mother, Father, I can't do it.
The library is beautiful.
If only we have this kind of library,
I can live here for the rest of my life.
I will read every day and, Mother, look.
They have a book about how to raise a llama,
when I don't even know what a llama is.
It looks like a mix of goat and giraffe.
I don't know that.
Only a fool will not read in a library
as beautiful as this.
Mother, there are a lot of books.
Mother, Father, this is one of
the famous places I see in GU.
Before, I only see this online,
but now here it is.
Tada...
It's the fountain!
The water is cold, Mother.
You know, Mother, Father,
there's a part in my heart that's sad
because I wasn't able to study here.
But half of my heart is excited
because next year,
I will try again to apply
so I can get into this school.
I will try again to fulfill all our dreams.
Mother, Father, join me, please.
And I promise you,
I will fulfill all of our dreams.
Everything.
And I will never get tired of dreaming.
You don't have to promise, Florence,
because your father and I believe
that you will fulfill
everything you want in life.
We're always here to support you.
Oh, Father, Mother, wait.
Mr. Dencio is calling.
Maybe he's looking for me.
Bye for now.
I love you, Mother, I love you, Father.
Mr. Dencio...
Hello, Mr. Dencio?
Hello, Florence.
Where are you?
Don Ferell has been looking for you
for a while now.
Is that so?
Okay, I'm on my way back.
Wait, Mr. Dencio!
Grandpa Garp, I'm sorry.
I lost track of time.
I just went for a stroll in the area.
GU is so beautiful, that's why,
I couldn't stop myself
from enjoying the area.
I also took a video call
with my mother and father,
because it's always been my dream
to get into this school.
- It's so beautiful...
- Florence, please stop.
You have to relax,
because I have something important
to tell you.
What's that?
Did I do something wrong?
Nothing. You didn't do anything wrong.
Dean, this is Florence Dela Cruz.
Florence, this is Dean Alvaro.
- Hello, Florence.
- Hello...
It's my pleasure to finally meet you.
We never get the chance
to know each other personally.
But I already know you,
Ms. Florence Dela Cruz,
because I personally reviewed and approved
your application for a scholarship.
- What?
- Yes.
Actually, Florence,
I had your background checked.
Excuse me, Don Ferell,
here is the background check
that we did for our new cook.
All information about her is there.
Very bright student.
Always gets the top honors...
She even got a scholarship at GU.
Don't take it personally that Serafica
did a background check on you.
That's standard for every new employee
who will enter our family.
The safety of my grandsons is paramount,
but when I was reviewing your information,
I saw the scholarship status
in the university.
That's why, I talked to Dean.
I'm sorry, Florence,
but I took the liberty of explaining
to Don Ferell your situation.
After all, he's one of the board members
of this university
and one of the biggest donors
in our Honors Program.
According to Dean,
you turned down the scholarship
because you needed to work
to help your father who, if I'm not mistaken,
have a heart problem.
Yes but he's doing okay now.
Yeah, but it still bothers me.
Sadly, an intelligent,
hardworking, and good student like you
is not in school.
That's why... I have a proposal for you.
You can still cook for us,
to help your family,
but now you have the option to study in GU,
if you want.
Really, Florence?
That's great news.
Are you sure about what Don Ferell said,
that he'll allow you to study
at the university
while working in their household as a cook?
I also can't believe it,
but that's what Grandpa Garp said.
Grandpa Garp?
That's what Don Ferell wants to be called.
Wow, and you're calling him Grandpa Garp too.
Maybe tomorrow and the day after,
you'll become a grandchild of Grandpa Garp.
But, my child,
can you manage to work and study
at the same time?
Won't you have a hard time?
Grandpa Garp's grandsons
are also studying in that school.
So if they're in school,
I don't have someone to cook for.
And the Dean also allowed me
not to take a full load of my first semester
so my schedule is lighter.
But your mother has a point.
You might exhaust yourself
and won't have time for yourself.
No, don't worry. I can handle that.
I, of all people, inherited your good traits.
Just make sure that you can
take care of yourself.
Yes, Mother.
I promise that you don't have to worry
because I can do this.
Okay, your father needs to rest,
and it's his turn to take care of himself.
Goodnight, my child.
I'm so happy for you.
I'm so happy too.
Goodnight, Mother. Goodnight, Father.
I love you both. I miss you.
Just a second.
Owen?
Florence, I heard the good news.
Why don't we celebrate?
Celebrate?
We'll drink?
I don't drink.
Who said we'll be drinking?
What's happening here?
Surprise.
I actually was the first to hear
the good news.
I overheard Grandpa Garp
and Ms. Serafica talking...
I heard about his plans
of letting you study in GU.
Don't worry, Florence.
Troy is already a good boy.
Right, Troy?
Really?
- Here.
- Thank you.
I'm also looking for a chance
to apologize to you.
I was one of the guys who played a prank
on your first day here in the mansion.
That's okay, forget about it.
I already forgot about it.
What happened that day?
Don't do that, never forget.
Or we'll keep doing our mistakes
from the past.
We must learn from history.
I, Aldus, and Tristan
were being jerks that day.
I feel really bad about it.
I hope I'll be okay with Tristan and Aldus,
and Nero too,
so I'll be cool with all the Ferells.
Isn't Nero okay with you?
Nero?
He's okay with me?
He always gives me dagger looks.
No way. He only looks mad,
but he's okay with you.
As a matter of fact,
he's one of your biggest defenders
here in the mansion.
- Nero?
- Yes.
My biggest defender?
How did that happen?
If you're enjoying at the expense of others,
that's not called fun.
You call that disrespectful.
Who are you? Are you her boyfriend?
Hey... Do I have to be her boyfriend
just to tell you
what you're doing is wrong?
It was he who confronted us
to stop us from playing a prank on you.
Oh, really?
Yes.
And not only that,
he was the first one to show support
for your cooking.
What do you think
of Florence's home cooked dish?
Is it good or should I fire her?
Because I won't force you
if you really don't like it,
there's nothing we can do.
But it's you who will decide.
It's you who will judge.
What do you say?
I like her...
I mean, I like her cooking.
And if I can have it my way,
I want her to stay as our cook.
That's good.
- You're right.
- I agree with you, Nero.
The food is delicious.
If I'm being honest,
I would've voted for you too,
but Nero got ahead of me.
Just say you got scared
because you're afraid...
that Aldus and Tristan will pick on you.
But we can't deny the fact that
it was Nero who first talked.
He was the first who showed support
for your cooking.
And we all know that
Nero is Grandpa's favorite,
that's why, when he said
that he likes your cooking,
well, no one's going to challenge that.
It's also not a stretch
to say that because of Nero,
up to now,
you're still the cook for the Ferells.
Because if not for him, you're already fired.
Do you think I'm scared of you?
I'm not scared of the Ferell brothers
and I don't care no matter who you are.
Is that so?
Project eliminate Florence Dela Cruz,
activated.
Ferell brothers, let's go!
Hey, what's with you.
Ouch! What are you doing?
Get your hands off me. Ouch! What's with you?
Let me go!
Thank you, Nero, thank you for saving me.
Thank you for choosing me over your brothers.
What's this again, Florence?
Stop this madness.
You've been thinking a lot of nonsense,
that's why, you're dreaming such things.
You're getting too much affected
by the Ferells.
We can't deny the fact that
it was Nero who first talked.
He was the first who showed support
for your cooking.
And we all know that
Nero is Grandpa's favorite,
that's why, when he said
that he likes your cooking,
well, no one's going to challenge that.
It's also not a stretch to say
that because of Nero,
up to now,
you're still the cook for the Ferells.
Because if not for him, you're already fired.
Sorry, Nero, for judging you.
You're okay even if you're a bit weird.
Okay, promise, I will not judge you again.
What's with you, Florence,
you get scared easily.
You better wake up.
Just calm down.
It's just me.
Why do you look that way?
This is part of my skincare process.
It's difficult to maintain my glowing skin.
Too much pressure,
especially since a lot of people is saying
I look so much like Gretchen Barretto.
What?
That's beside the point.
My point is why are you up early?
Bad dream?
Not really, I just jolted out of sleep,
and in a few hours, the sun will be up.
I thought of starting work early.
Well then let me take this opportunity
to tell you that Don Ferell and I
talked already
about sending you to school.
I was planning to talk to you.
I just want to let you know that even though
I'll be going to GU,
I will not neglect my work here.
Very good then,
I guess we won't have a problem.
Nero?
He's early.
Where is he going?
How are you?
Are you hungry?
Here.
Just eat up.
Is that not enough?
Hey, you, I thought a ghost is scaring me,
but it's just you.
Never ever give up.
You can do this.
Doves?
It's you again?
You even woke me up.
Don't get tired of dreaming.
He's the one sending me messages?
Do you want music?
Do you want some music? Okay.
There you go.
Join me.
Who's there?
It's just you.
Come here.
I've been looking for you.
I thought you were preyed on by other birds.
You're hungry already?
Come here, I will feed you.
It's just you, I thought it was someone else.
Come here.
Hey, you, I miss you.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
It's you again?
You even woke me up.
Don't get tired of dreaming.
So it was Nero who was sending me
those secret messages?
He is defending me.
He only looks mad, but he's okay with you.
As a matter of fact,
he's one of your biggest defenders
here in the mansion.
He confronted us to stop picking on you.
He also wants my cooking.
Because of Nero, up to now,
you're still the cook for the Ferells.
Because if not for him,
you're probably fired by now.
And he sends me a message using a dove.
Hey, you.
I thought a ghost is scaring me
when it was just you.
Never ever give up.
You can do it.
What's that?
He likes me, as in...
he wants me to be his girlfriend, is that it?
So?
What will the grandsons have?
Adobong Kalapati.
Is this a joke?
No, I mean I'll be cooking adobado.
Adobado?
Do you mean Adobo?
- Well?
- Yes.
Okay, just make sure
you'll cook for Dencio too.
Adobo.
Adobado...
Go ahead and eat, sir.
Don't call me sir.
Just Nero.
Okay, sir, I mean Nero.
This looks delicious.
I'm hungry.
Florence, why don't you join us?
No, thank you, Grandpa Garp.
I promised Mr. Dencio I'll be joining them.
Have you talked to Serafica
about your scholarship at the university?
Yes, everything is okay.
That's very good.
You're in your freshman year in college,
Florence,
so we're just the same.
What's your department?
Com Arts.
Com Arts?
It's fun there.
Nero likes people from Com Arts.
Don't tease Florence.
And, Florence, you better be careful.
If you see Nero in the Com Arts building,
you better hide.
I don't think it's a good joke, Tristan.
We're making things awkward for Florence.
No, Owen, it's okay.
Besides, I'm not fond of the Ferells.
Oh, burn.
But, Nero, you already have an advantage.
Because if there's someone you like
from Com Arts Department,
I can act as a bridge.
Oh.
Why don't you act as a bridge for each other?
Sure.
Perfect, there's someone I like.
"Sure. Perfect, there's someone I like."
What? Are we going to eat
or we'll discuss Nero's love life?
Aldus is right.
Let's eat before this delicious dish
Florence cooked gets cold.
Let's go, guys.
Go!
Florence, let's eat.
Mr. Dencio, you know that whenever I cook,
I always taste the food.
That's why after cooking, I'm already full.
So, you have no appetite.
Oh my, I might think that you're in love.
It's the opposite,
when I'm in love, the more I eat.
Why?
Have you been in love?
Yes, of course.
Oh, really?
You're still young.
And if you've been in love before,
when and to whom?
- That's right.
- I'm in love every day
because I love my mother and father.
- I love my family so much.
- No wonder.
Good answer.
Speaking of... I'll just call my parents...
the people I love in my life.
Hello, Mother, Father.
Hello, Florence!
Your mother and I were thinking,
what gift can we give Don Ferell
for his kindness to you as a thank you gift.
That's why we thought of
giving him a gift certificate.
Oh, how about a teddy bear?
Or small cars for his small grandsons?
Yes.
Mother, Father, that's not needed anymore.
Are you sure?
I'm worried about these gift certificates,
they might expire.
Mother, Father,
there's nothing we can give
that Grandpa Garp needs.
Maybe you've forgotten,
he owns half of our town.
How about a soul?
Does he need a soul?
Ours are available.
You're full of jokes.
Okay, why don't we do this, Florence?
If you can think of anything
that the mansion needs
that your father and I can give,
just let us know.
So we can give something
as a token of gratitude
for the Ferells' kindness to you.
Yes, Mother.
How about you?
How are you doing there?
Yes, is there a new rumor?
Nothing much but...
But what?
Is that Serafica treating you badly?
Just tell me and I'll confront that witch.
No, Mother,
there's just something I want to ask you.
Florence, how many times
should I explain to you
that the sun is the center
of the solar system
and moving around it are the planets...
Just take it easy...
Hold on.
- Here, water first.
- Father, are you okay?
Yes, he's doing okay, Florence.
Don't worry, Father,
my question is not about the solar system.
It's just about...
about my friend.
Who's that friend of yours?
It's Jenny.
Jenny?
Jennylyn?
Jennylyn Mercado?
You're now friends with Jennylyn Mercado?
No, it's not Jennylyn Mercado...
It's Jenny.
Never mind, you're just making
a fool out of me.
It's your fault,
you're fooling your daughter.
No, go ahead, Florence.
What's the problem with
that Jennylyn Mercado,
I mean, Jenny.
Well, it's because someone
is sending her secret messages.
Are these obscene pictures?
No, Father, these are just ordinary messages,
something like words of wisdom.
It's inspiring and makes you feel better.
What's the problem?
She discovered the person
who is sending those secret messages.
What will she do?
Should she confront the person?
Should she talk to the person
and ask why he's doing that?
Why is he sending her messages
if he has a secret motive?
A secret desire?
You know, Florence,
there's only one thing your father and I
can say about that.
Bring it to DJ Acapulco.
Good Morning to our listeners and viewers,
because we are simulcast live via UTobe.
And thank you to the 55,000 concurrent views,
that's awesome.
Perfect to start our program.
So, for our first messenger,
what is your favorite color?
The question is so corny,
but of course, Fuschia.
But if you'll ask me how to spell it,
never mind.
I'll just say red. Anyway,
let's go to our second message.
Her question is interesting.
Will I confront the person
who is sending me secret messages?
The messages are actually sweet and nice.
And should he know that I know
that he's sending me secret messages?
From Jenny.
Could Jennylyn Mercado send this message?
I'm pretty sure she has
a lot of secret admirers.
Anyway, you know, Jenny,
some people are having a hard time
showing their feelings.
That's why sometimes,
some resort to secret messages.
And what I can advise you is,
don't confront him yet.
Give him time and eventually,
he will have the courage to face you
and tell what he truly feels for you.
And when the time is right,
he will personally shout out to the world
his love for you.
But for now,
just let him secretly express his feelings
through secret messages.
There you go,
Jennylyn Mercado just needs time
and a chance for her secret admirer.
I disagree because I understand
what Jennylyn Mercado is going through.
If that's how truly he feels about her,
then why can't he tell the truth?
Why does it have to be a secret?
"There's a secret message"?
If I know, maybe he has a wife,
that's why he's keeping it a secret.
We can't assume right away
the worst in people.
Oh please, spare me.
Again, I disagree.
Men can't be trusted.
If their intentions were true,
why won't they show themselves?
That's why as for me, swipe right away
if the man has no picture
and no description in his profile.
Don Ferell, it's you...
I'm sorry, Don Ferell.
Is there anything you need, Sir,
that's why you came to our nest?
I just want to talk to Florence.
We have something important to talk about.
Okay, we'll leave you behind, Don Ferell.
You better stay.
You're included here. You're involved too.
Did I do something bad?
Sir, if Florence did something wrong,
I will take full responsibility.
After all, she's under me.
And whatever mistake she did
is because of me,
so I'll be the one to punish her.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I only have a request, actually.
I want you to cook chopsuey for me.
Huh?
That's my favorite,
but ever since my wife died,
I haven't tasted a delicious chopsuey.
Of course, Don Ferell, we can do that.
No problem.
Actually, I don't want to contradict myself.
Remember we agreed that Florence
will decide what to cook for this household.
But please grant the request of an old man.
I'm longing for the previous life
I had with my beloved wife.
Is that all?
No problem. It's just a small thing.
Small thing?
She means nothing to worry about.
She can do it.
This means to say,
you'll be needing freshly picked vegetables,
because that's how Dona Ferell used to do it.
She gets the vegetables
from the Ferell's farms.
You can go to the farm early morning,
tomorrow.
From what I heard,
our produce is ready for harvest.
I'll ask Nero to drive you.
What?
Nero?
I'll ask Mr. Dencio.
Dencio and I are going somewhere.
How about Mr. James?
Oh, I'm sorry, I'll be using James tomorrow
because I have an important appointment
in the spa.
I can commute.
Don't give yourself a hard time.
I can ask Nero to bring you there.
And he is known in that place,
he grew up there.
My grandson is sulking, so let him go out
of his dugout once in a while
and get some sunlight
so that he can have vitamin D.
I agree.
That's so correct, Don Ferell.
Okay, no problem.
I'll ask Nero to go with me tomorrow.
♪ Chopsuey... Chopsuey ♪
Florence, what's for breakfast?
There, it's right in front of you,
ready to bite you.
Happy Morning, Troy and Owen.
- What do you want to eat?
- Wait a second.
Why is there favoritism here?
I thought you'll never visit us here.
Is that possible?
Who are you with?
I'm Florence Dela Cruz.
I'm the cook in the mansion right now.
Mother told me that often than not,
the outside appearance is different
from what's inside.
So if you want to know them better,
you should knock on their hearts.
Let me ask you.
What if the person
whose heart you're knocking
refuses to let you in his life?
I will just keep on knocking...
Knock, knock, knock until he opens the door.
If I need to shout, I will shout.
Hey, let me in your heart!